Leo：From the bottom of our hearts, we promise that from here on out
Vanessa 对世界造成的危机解除后，已经过了三个月
It's already been three months since the crisis that Vanessa threatened the world with was averted...
Leo：敝社承诺今后将不会再祕密地使用古文明科技
A.R.C. stated that they would abolish the Library's facilities
A.R.C. 宣布将 Library 的设施废止
Leo：and will be transparent with all the content of our research
Leo：并会公开透明化所有研究内容
and use other types of server technology to replace the operations of the virtual internet
并使用其他伺服器技术取代精神网路的营运
Leo：Starting today, we will implement serious changes to our internal structure
Leo：今后敝社将会进行内部改革
Leo：For the development of society and humanity
Leo：为了社会与人类的发展
Of course, lots of people found this unacceptable and denounced the organization
许多人无法接受，予以指责
Leo：we will seriously reconsider our position in society and the direction we are headed...
Leo：重新思考我们的定位和方向……
Especially those who lost their loved ones as a result of what happened
尤其是因为这次事件失去心爱之人的人们
But after a period of time most people returned to their normal lives
但大部份的人仍在一段时间后恢復了原本正常的生活
Time gradually diluted all that had occurred
时间也逐渐冲淡这一切
After graduating from university, NEKO became a professional streamer musician
NEKO 从学院毕业后，成为了职业的编曲实况主
Besides her normal content of music, games and random gossip
内容除了熟悉的音乐、游戏与八卦
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Yo-ho! NEKO's here!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：唷嗬！NEKO 登场！
she also started a new series
也开设了新的系列节目
where she actively goes out to help the victims that were affected by Vanessa
主动关心且帮助那些因 Vanessa 事件而受到伤害的人们
Victim：We don't need help from you internet addicts. Please, go away...
受害者：我们不需要你们这些网路成瘾者的帮助，请回吧……
Although she is constantly rejected, she never gives up
虽然屡遭拒绝，不过她并未放弃
She used money she made from her music and streams to set up a foundation
用音乐与直播赚的钱成立了基金会
that donates to the people affected and related illnesses
对相关人士以及病症进行捐献
Xenon started playing with a band again and got back on the stage to perform
Xenon 重启了乐团活动，再次登上舞台表演
NEKO can always be seen among the crowd
观众席裡总是能见到 NEKO 的身影
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Not bad~!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：辛苦啦～！
As for Xenon's sister Shannon,
Xenon 的妹妹 Shannon
she gradually shed the effect that the virtual internet had on her
在事件后逐渐脱离了精神网路的影响
and her condition started to improve
病情开始好转
A.R.C. kept begging Xenon to return
A.R.C. 不断恳求 Xenon 回去
But no matter how generous their offers were, no matter what position they promised
然而，不管他们提供了多麽优渥的待遇与职位
Xenon refused to accept
Xenon 始终没有答应
After the dissolution of Baro,
在 Baro 帮瓦解后，JOEZ Cafe 在圈内的地位越来越高
JOE's way of doing things became more and more like Saxon's
JOE 也越来越有 Saxon 的架式
Mr. Neumann decided to move to Node 13,
ConneR 决定移居到 Node 13
continuing to research the unsolved mysteries of his ancestors with Sasha
与 Sasha 继续研究自己祖先历史中未解的谜团
Humanity was still curious about ancient technology and yearned to learn more
人类仍对古文明科技充满好奇与嚮往
The missions of A.R.C.'s Exploration Team continued
A.R.C. 探勘队的任务也还在持续中
ConneR：Oh? You again?
ConneR：什麽？是你呀？
ConneR：Keep up the hard work
ConneR：真是辛苦了
Rin was able to break free of A.R.C.'s control,
Rin 脱离了 A.R.C. 的控制
concealing her Architect identity and living with Sagar
并隐藏了自己建造者的身份，与 Sagar 生活在一起
She also returned to Node 03 to look for her past memories
她也回到 Node 03 寻找自己过去的回忆
Rin：Ah! Oh...
Rin：呀！啊……
Rin：I'm s-so sorry!
Rin：非、非常对不起！
Rin：Wah!
Rin：哇！
Daigo：Chief, here's the part you asked for
Daigo：组长，您要的零件在这裡
Nora returned to Kyuu Hou Kai and led research in various fields of medicine
Nora 回到玖凰会，主导各种医疗科技的研发
Nora：Thank you, just put it there
Nora：谢谢，放在那边就好
all the while trying to repair ROBO_Head
同时也试着修復 ROBO_Head
Nora："NORA"
Nora：「NORA」
Helena was unable to accept the loss of PAFF and Noah, remaining mired in sorrow,
Helena 无法接受 PAFF 与 Noah 逝去的事实，沉浸在悲伤中
all alone
孤独一人
Hayato remained in the "music world", as promised,
Hayato 留在约定好的「音乐世界」
missing Kaori through music
藉由音乐思念着 Kaori
Though sorrow and regret remains,
儘管悲伤、遗憾仍存在
everyone is still working hard to live their lives
但人们还是努力地过着生活
The world still turns,
世界依然运转
just as before.
一如往常